okay so we are now going to talk about
好的，所以我们现在要谈论
setting which will be analyzed quite
设置将进行相当多的分析
extensively basically for the rest of
基本上，其余的
the course in terms of the types of
该课程的类型
mechanisms we're going to be looking at
我们将要研究的机制
and the alternative games we're looking
以及我们正在寻找的替代游戏
at and in particular what this is known
特别是在什么地方
as is a setting with transferrable
与可转让的设置一样
utility and what's looked at in these
实用程序以及这些内容
settings are situations where what
设置是什么情况
people have what's known as quasi linear
人们有所谓的准线性
preferences and the idea and before we
偏好和想法以及我们之前
get into the formal definitions is that
进入正式定义是
there's something like money some
有一些钱
transferrable good that we can move back
我们可以转移的可转让商品
and forth between agents and we know
代理商之间来回，我们知道
that that how much that's worth to them
那对他们来说值多少钱
and we can trade that off versus utility
我们可以权衡实用性
and that gives us a nice sort of private
这给了我们一种很好的私人
good that we can move back and forth
好，我们可以来回移动
sort of payments in an auction or
拍卖中的付款方式或
payments contributions to a public good
对公共物品的缴款
and we'll assume that that translates
我们假设
directly into some utility numbers and
直接放入一些实用程序编号中
the importance of doing that is it's
这样做的重要性在于
going to give us a lot of power in terms
将会给我们很多力量
of aligning incentives by making
通过制定激励措施
people's payments encapsulate the
人民付款封装了
externalities that they're imposing on
他们施加的外部性
others for in terms of decisions so once
其他人的决定，所以一次
we have transferable utility it'll give
我们有可转让的实用程序
us a lot of power and designing
我们很多力量和设计
mechanisms in terms of making sure we
确保我们的机制
basically price everything and we can
基本上定价一切，我们可以
figure out what kinds of prices people
弄清楚人们的价格类型
should be paying to change one decision
应该为改变一个决定而付出
to another decision and that's going to
另一个决定，这将
be a very useful tool in designing
成为设计中非常有用的工具
mechanisms as we go forward okay so what
我们前进的机制好吗
are the formal definitions look like
正式的定义是什么样子
instead of just having some abstract set
而不只是设置一些抽象
of outcomes
结果的
now the outcomes are going to have
现在的结果将是
structure where there will still be some
仍然会有一些结构
some basic sort of public aspect to it
基本的公共方面
some decision X and then the other part
一些决定X，然后是另一部分
is going to be a set of real numbers
将是一组实数
where we give each individual some
我们给每个人一些
payment or may have them make up payment
付款或可以让他们补付款
so there's some transfers going on
所以有一些转移
between the different individuals and so
在不同的个体之间等等
we will have some list RN of what those
我们将有一些清单RN
payments are so
付款是如此
in in this particular setting when we
在这种特殊的情况下，当我们
have quasi linear preferences so people
有准线性偏好，所以人们
have quasi linear so here what we're
具有准线性，所以在这里
going to have is things are going to be
将要发生的事情将是
linear in this second dimension so we
在第二维上是线性的，所以我们
can think of an outcome now as being a
现在可以认为结果是
list of what's the public decision some
什么是公共决策清单
X and a and X and then also some P which
X和a和X然后还有一些P
is going to be a p1 through PN of what
通过PN成为p1
those payments are and a given
这些付款是给定的
individuals utility for the outcome can
个人对结果的效用可以
be split into a utility function which
分成一个实用函数
describes how they like the x's and then
描述他们如何喜欢x，然后
also they subtract off whatever payment
他们也减去任何付款
they're making and that payment could be
他们正在付款，付款可能是
positive or negative so it could be that
正面或负面，所以可能是
they're paying something to into this
他们为此付出了一些代价
society - as part of the outcome or it
社会-作为结果的一部分
could be that they're receiving payments
可能是他们正在收款
and these payments are going to be very
这些付款将非常
important in designing efficient
在设计高效方面很重要
mechanisms designing mechanisms to align
设计协调机制的机制
people's incentives with what we'd like
人们想要的激励
okay so quasi linearity gives us a lot
好吧，所以准线性给了我们很多
of power you can see where the quasi
的力量，你可以看到准
linearity where's the linearity part of
线性度是哪里的线性度
this linearity part is that the
这个线性部分是
Preferences are always just moving
偏好总是在变化
linearly with whatever this payment
与这笔付款成线性关系
scheme is whatever the money dimension
计划是金钱的任何方面
is okay so when we start talking about
没关系，所以当我们开始谈论时
mechanisms in this world then we can
在这个世界上的机制，那么我们可以
split the mechanism into making a choice
将机制分解为做出选择
so it's going to choose something so
所以要选择一些东西
I've got our outcomes are equal to X
我得到的结果等于X
cross RN so what it's doing is is first
穿越RN，所以首先要做的是
of all going to make a choice out of the
所有人将从中做出选择
X and then also have payments in an RN
X，然后在RN中付款
so X and X is a non-monetary outcome and
所以X和X是非货币结果，
we'll use the term money here it's not
我们将在这里使用金钱一词，不是
clear exactly what the transferable good
明确清楚什么是可转让的商品
is but there's some way of moving
是，但是有某种方式可以移动
something back and forth which people
来回回事的人
can equate with utility so there's some
可以等同于效用，所以有一些
non-monetary outcome so often these are
非货币结果，通常是
called public decisions the aspect which
将公共决策称为
is going to be common to all the agents
对所有代理商来说都是共同的
and then we've got these private
然后我们将这些私人
payments where each person is making a
每个人都在付款的地方
payment into the mechanism and if P is
付款到机制中，如果P是
negative then that means they're
否定则表示他们是
actually getting a net payment to them
实际得到他们的净付款
and the implications in terms of making
以及在制作方面的含义
this kind of assumption in terms of
这种假设是
these preferences first of all the
这些偏好首先
utility that somebody has for this
有人为此提供的实用程序
outcome can be separated out from the
结果可以与
utility that they get from the payment
他们从付款中获得的效用
so it's not influenced by the amount of
因此不受数量的影响
money or wealth an agent has and second
代理人拥有的金钱或财富，其次
secondly they people care a given agent
其次，他们会照顾给定的代理商
cares only about X and their payment P I
只关心X及其付款PI
they don't care about say P J where J is
他们不在乎说PJ在哪里
not equal to I right so they don't care
不等于我是对的，所以他们不在乎
what payments other people are making
别人在做什么
they just care about what's the overall
他们只是在乎整体
decision which candidate do we pick or
决定我们选哪个候选人或
which public good do we pick or what
我们该选择哪种公共物品？
decision are we making in terms of who
我们是根据谁来做决定
gets what good and in what payment do I
得到什么好处，我该用什么付款
have to make and I don't care what other
必须制造，我不在乎
people's payments are to the extent that
人们的付款范围是
doesn't enter into my payment okay so
不能进入我的付款范围，所以
that's the setting and then direct
那是设置，然后直接
mechanism in this world is going to be a
这个世界上的机制将是
combination of some choice some X theta
一些选择的组合，一些X theta
which comes out of X and a payment
由X和付款产生
scheme as a function of the Thetas so
方案作为Thetas的函数
now we announced our Thetas and then
现在我们宣布了Thetas，然后
Society spits back at us a public
社会向我们吐口水
decision this non-monetary decision and
决定此非货币决定，并
then a list of transfers or payments
然后是转帐或付款清单
that were each going to make okay so
每个都可以，所以
that's a direct mechanism one thing
这是一种直接的机制
that's going to be very useful in these
在这些中这将非常有用
kinds of settings and a lot of the
各种设置以及很多
analysis that we do going forward will
我们进行的分析将
be in a special case of quasi linearity
在准线性的特殊情况下
and when we're thinking about the
当我们在考虑
utility that individuals have so we have
个人拥有的效用
now we're writing people's utility over
现在我们在写人们的效用
all as a utility of what the X's and the
全部用作X和
theta minus P I of theta right so and
theta减去theta的PI，所以
this X can depend on theta what we're
这个X可以取决于theta我们是什么
gonna do now is we're gonna make a look
现在要做的是我们要看看
at situations where there's a further
在有进一步的情况
assumption made where instead of having
假设在哪里而不是
people's preferences depend on the full
人们的喜好取决于全部
vector of types in the society it's
社会中类型的向量
going to depend only on their own type
只取决于自己的类型
so a will say that preferences have
所以会说偏好
private values or satisfy conditional
私人价值或满足条件
utility independence
效用独立性
if a particular person eyes utility
如果某人眼睛有用
function depends only on theta I okay so
功能仅取决于theta我可以，所以
the utility for this overall outcome
总体结果的实用程序
does not depend on anybody else's type
不取决于其他人的类型
it only depends on my own type so that
这只取决于我自己的类型
means that once I know my own theta I
表示一旦我知道了自己的theta
know everything about my preferences and
知道我的喜好和
what this rules out is things like
排除的是类似
investing in a stock where I'm not quite
投资我不很喜欢的股票
sure what the value of that investment
确定那笔投资的价值
is I don't know how well it's going to
我不知道会怎么样
pay off and other people might have
还清，其他人可能有
information that would be very valuable
有价值的信息
to me that's ruled out here once I know
对我来说，一旦我知道就排除在这里
my information I know everything I need
我的信息我知道我需要的一切
to know about my preferences and nobody
知道我的喜好，没人
else's information enters into that
其他信息进入
preference calculation okay so if we're
偏好计算可以，如果我们
talking about a particular candidate I
谈论一个特定的候选人
know whether I like this candidate or
知道我是否喜欢这个候选人或
not or if it's a public good I know
不是，或者我知道这是公共利益
whether I want that cup public good
我是否想要那杯公共物品
though so what that's what's nice about
但是，那是什么呢？
the private good setting is now instead
现在改为私人物品
of just thinking about theta eyes we can
只想着θ的眼睛
think of just people just telling us
想到人们只是告诉我们
what their utility function looks like
它们的效用函数是什么样的
so we can think of the the private
所以我们可以想到私人
information they have is just a
他们拥有的信息仅仅是
valuation function VI of X which is
X的估值函数VI为
equivalent to this UI of X of theta I so
等效于theta X的用户界面，因此
the theta just becomes telling us what
theta只是告诉我们什么
that function is okay so agents have a
该功能还可以，因此业务代表可以
valuation function which is basically
估值函数基本上是
they are the value that they have of any
它们是他们所拥有的任何价值
particular allocation X okay and so then
特定的分配X好的，然后
when we start thinking about direct
当我们开始考虑直接
mechanisms we can think of the space of
我们可以想到的机制
individuals that the private information
个人认为私人信息
individuals have as these V is so in
个人有这样的V
particular everybody can tell us instead
特别是每个人都可以告诉我们
of a type they tell us now their
他们现在告诉我们他们的类型
valuation function and the standard
评估功能和标准
notation we'll use is that people will
我们将使用的符号是人们会
tell us some V hat I which might be a
告诉我们一些V帽我可能是
lie
位于
so dominant-strategy mechanisms they
如此重要的战略机制
might not always exist it could be that
可能并不总是存在，可能是
people are going to tell us some
人们会告诉我们一些
alternate evaluation function instead of
替代评估功能代替
the true valuation function and so we
真正的估值函数，所以我们
can look at when is it that they're
可以看看他们什么时候
going to want to tell us their true
要告诉我们他们的真实情况
valuation function so now we ask people
估值功能，所以现在我们问人们
what how do you value these different
您如何看待这些不同之处
alternatives and under this private
替代品和这种私人
value or conditional independent
价值或条件独立
conditional utility independence
有条件的效用独立性
condition they know their own
他们知道自己的条件
preferences
首选项
and they can tell us what that
他们可以告诉我们那
preference function is and then we can
偏好函数是，然后我们可以
look at mechanism design and ask it when
看一下机制设计并询问何时
is it that possible and now this quasi
是否有可能，现在这种准
linear world with these private values
具有这些私人价值的线性世界
to get people to truthfully tell us what
让人们如实告诉我们
their preferences look like
他们的喜好看起来